missrebel.co.uk 2014-05-05

# Customer Care - Womens Clothing Sale, Womens Fashion, Cheap Clothes Online | Miss Rebel

Missrebel has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you become a member is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

## **Information We Collect**

In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

  * i. Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  * ii. Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase. 
  * iii. Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

## **Registration**

We do not require that you provide any information, nor create a username and password other than for purposes of purchasing products from our web site. In addition, the option of creating a username and password is provided only in the event that customers plan to use our site to purchase products from our web site in the future and would like to keep their contact information on file with us for that purpose. Upon registering, users will receive confirmation that their information has been placed on file with us and, when applicable, a username and password have been created. Your address details are not required for registration and will only be required during a purchase from Missrebel.

## **Orders**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

## **Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  * i. To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
  * ii. To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information. 
  * iii. To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.

If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in. 

Where your consent has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you. Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.

Any information you provide will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes other than order fulfillment 

## **Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information**

After becoming a My Company member you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the 'My Account' link. The changes you make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, please contact us trough the 'Contact Us' section.

## **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * We do not share aggregated demographic information about our userbase with our partners and advertisers. 
  * We only store information that you provide and choose to store in your account profile. We do not share your profile with other third parties.
  * We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
  * We use WORLDPAY to provide credit card processing on our site. WORLDPAY is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  * In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
  * Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
  * To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud

## **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email to us at customerservice@missrebel.co.uk.

## **Site Security**

All Missrebel employees take your personal information very seriously. All employees must learn and obey our security policies. Access to member personal information is limited to key management personnel and our customer services department.

## **Credit Card Information**

We use WORLDPAY Payment Gateway System (www.worldpay.com) to verify your credit card billing information, in order to ensure that the user is the person identified on the credit card and to insure against fraud. **Credit Card details are only required during a purchase from our website. The details are only used for processing by WORLDPAY. We do not see or store your credit card details on our site.**

## **Promotional Emails**

From time to time we may send out email messages on products, special deals & promotions, if and only if you have opted in to our email newsletter. In addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional materials. If you choose to receive our Newsletters, they will contain promotional materials from Missrebel

## **Newsletters**

When you register with Missrebel you are given the choice of opting in to our newsletter, which provides information about special offers, promotions and product announcements. We also provide the option of creating a username and password if you wish to keep your information on file with us for intent of doing business with us again. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at customerservice@missrebel.co.uk. 

## **Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

## **Customer Service**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

## **Our Use of Log Files**

When you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiableinformation.

## **Our Use of Cookies**

Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer fin order to assist us in improving our website. We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer's hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer. 

The ability to select products on our site is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in aggregate form. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.

## **Links To Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving the My missrebel.co.uk and entering another Web site. These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## **Business Transitions**

In the event Missrebel goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

## **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site

## **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by telephoning (00)44 1924 469716 or emailing us at customerservice@missrebel.co.uk.
